Love me, love me.
Hate me, hate me.
Kill me, kill me.
I'm so, I'm so, listen at this great
old Tokyo world's love and hate.
Move away, move away.
These times, no living
ashamed as it's been all away.
I'm so, I'm so, I love and hate.
Download track, so mark, so one way.
One way, turn away. It's my own.
Sayonara till we meet the show.
Too dramatic, did we roll down in there?
Now there's someone that still
finished me that was there.
Came consumed in the fiction.
The descendants of lies and truth we run.
This broken love now might
you forget this thing?
Can I not mind cause I will
survive the stage that's there?
This underdog song, high tension.
Yet I won't say no way now if
I'm always beating them right.
Love me, love me.
Believe only what's right, K.
Hate me, hate me.
Feel that all away.
Love me, love me.
I'm so on love and hate.
You'll make you mean.
Come check me out of this way.
I'm so, I'm so deeply embraced.
Such tough beats of this love and hate.
We received and deceived.
We ourselves know that it's all fine.
I don't care the cost though.
I'm so, I'm so smiling awake.
It goes, I'm so full of love and hate.
Everything ends unknown.
It's my luck, I am all up.
Till we need a shot.
Well look who it is and what
an ugly face you've got there?
I'm pretty sure it's beyond fixing.
What are you planning to do, Maki?
You mean you can actually tell
women apart by their faces?
I thought you only saw their asses.
I'm asking you what you're going to do.
So answer me, you piece of trash.
You can't use sorcery.
You can't see cursed spirits.
The looks you had going
for you are ruined.
No one is ever going to
pay attention to you again.
Such a sad situation.
Shall I bully you like I used to?
What are you going to do?
Cling to the shadow of Okotsu or Megumi?
Say something, trash.
Maki, come back.
Have you forgotten?
You know very well that we're not
allowed entry into the Forbidden Vault.
Don't worry, the clan
head gave me permission.
Head of the Zenin clan? Me?
Yeah, it was in Naobito's will.
No thanks, it'll just be a hassle.
I think you should accept.
Naobito said he would entrust all
of the Zenin clan's assets to you,
both the money and the cursed tools.
If you become head of the clan,
you'll be able to get info on the big
three families and their headquarters.
It'll make a huge difference in
what we can do from here on out.
Sounds like you should do it, Maki.
You can have it.
Yeah, well, no one's going to
accept me as the head of the clan.
No one's gonna follow me yet.
The fact is, you possess
the hereditary technique,
and you can activate your domain,
and you received lots of attention from
Satoru, but they would barely accept you.
Why do I need their acceptance?
Does it even matter what the members
of the Zenin clan think about it?
You'd get all those benefits if you became
the head too, so just do it already.
It's too soon.
Can't be me yet.
I wouldn't be able to
create a place for Mai.
All right, fine.
Come back here!
Tell me why!
Tell me why must you
always be like this, Maki!
Just this once.
Make me happy I gave birth to you, Maki.
Father.
You should have said something if you
were planning this from the get-go.
You jumped the gun like always.
Though I agree Megumi Fushiguro
would be better than you.
Excuse me?
There's more than a few
voices pushing for him as
a chance to repair relations
with the Gojo clan.
But you know there's no way
we could accept Fushiguro
being entrusted with all
the money and cursed tools.
Then why were you dilly-dallying?
Because Fushiguro, in addition to
the Gojo clan, has other alliances.
He's friendly with Noritoshi,
the next head of the Kamo clan.
If we eliminate him without cause, it
would put the Zenin clan in a worse spot.
With Satoru Gojo sealed away,
and the power balance between clans
shifting will fall - I get all that,
but what I don't is why do it now?
You haven't read the notices
from headquarters yet, have you?
We can make use of that.
Label them as traitors plotting to
release Satoru Gojo, and then Megumi,
Maki, and Mai can be killed.
That's an impressive plan.
Killing his own daughters
adds believability.
It will.
Afterwards, the trust that Headquarters
places in us will grow firmer.
And is old man Ogi okay with all of this?
Ogi came up with this plan.
There are no cursed tools here, Maki.
We emptied our vault in
anticipation of your intentions.
Why did you come here?
You idiot.
Do you know why they
named my older brother
Naobito the previous head
of the Klan instead of me?
I'm guessing because you're an asshole
who would murder his own children.
You never wondered why I was
passed over as head of the clan?
How it was because my
two children I know why
we're such hopeless
failures broke his blade.
You broke my blade and judged
that my reach had been shortened.
So you closed in on me.
This is why you're hopeless.
I'm not a swordsman.
I'm a sorcerer.
Trying to gauge me by the standards of
such a failure is absolutely ridiculous.
I'll say it as many times as I must.
I wasn't chosen to be the previous head
of the clan because of the two of you.
My older brother's technique
was nothing to speak of.
and his potential to inherit the
clan was never a point of contention.
As a jujutsu sorcerer, I never lagged
behind my brother in any area except one.
The quality of my two children.
The one rule for children.
Never drag down your parents.
Didn't you know?
Dragging each other down is
considered a virtue in this country.
This room is used for
training and punishment.
We keep countless grade two and
lower cursed spirits in here.
They're hiding now because
they're afraid of me,
but soon enough they'll crawl
out and begin to devour you.
A heavenly pact?
Enhanced physical prowess?
What of it?
We sorcerers train every day,
and we further strengthen our
bodies with cursed energy in combat.
Maki, your power's ordinary.
But you possess every single
one of us already has.
Good riddance to the
soul's stain on my life.
Maki, you certainly are tough.
I always figured it would
come to this one day.
This really sucks.
You basically know at this point
what my technique can do, right?
Although I still have trouble creating
anything too large or complicated.
I'm wounded from where he cut me to.
So after I create this, I'll die.
Later.
good luck on your own
after this hey my wait
what are you talking
about just come back here
i've known for a long time now why twins
are considered to be such an unfortunate
accident by Jujutsu sorcerers you have to
offer up something in
order to gain anything
this goes beyond just pacts the fact that
we go through pain to
grow stronger follows
the same logic but that balance never
functions properly in
the case of twins like us
because jujutsu views
identical twins as the same
individual do you understand
you are me and i am you you
can long to grow stronger
and work so hard you spit
up blood but it's all pointless
because i don't want to
grow stronger at all even if
you don't have any techniques
it's pointless if i have
one so long as i exist maki
you will always be incomplete
okay i get it just come
back this is all i'll leave
you with cast off the rest
I'll take all the cursed energy
And everything else with me, too
Just promise me one thing
Please
Destroy everything
All of it, you hear?
Big sister
Mai, Mai,
Mai, wake up, Mai, wake up, Mai,
wake up, Mai,
wake up, Mai, wake up,
Mai, wake up, Mai.
The cursed spirits were
exercised, but my body remembers.
I worked so hard to forget that fear.
Technique release.
Blazing courage.
Very well, then.
This time I'll burn you down, right to
the marrow of your bones with my own hand!
Come, you f...
Okay, Mai, let's get started.
Ugh.
Why is it so noisy?
Jinichi!
Maki has lost her mind!
She murdered Ogi!
The Kukuru unit is on it now!
I guess even Ogi can be
caught off guard if he's
attacked in his sleep or
sitting on the toilet.
Capture her before I get there.
Sir!
If we dawdle too much,
Jinichi will become so smug I'll
never hear the end of it from him.
Oh, don't kill her yet.
I'll finish her myself.
The kukuru, are you listening?
The young men of the Zenin clan who don't
possess techniques are obligated to join.
And the martial arts are drilled into them
day and night so they
can serve under the hay.
What are you going to do?
I wonder what I plan to do.
Visual confirmation of two
unidentified cursed tools!
Maki had also been a member
until she joined Jujutsu High.
Why couldn't you just stay at the
bottom with me, Maki? You were right.
Staying at the bottom.
I'm sure that would have
been the right choice for us!
I'm sorry.
Just promise me one thing!
Please destroy everything?
All of it, you hear?
No!
Oh, my God.
LALALALA!
Hey, how's it coming along?
She went for the jackpot.
That's Chojuro's technique
The Hei are here The Hei They are
composed of those whose abilities
are recognized as semi-grade one or
higher by Jujutsu High Standards,
the Zenin Clan's strongest
collection of sorcerers.
How is she so moving after
taking Chojuro's attack?
She's pressed.
Easily broke through my guard.
I don't believe it!
Is she really the same Maki?
Jinichi!
Keep holding her there, Ronda!
I can't keep holding her.
Forget about me, GDG!
The current Zenin clan only exists.
Thanks to the women told me.
You must have realized it by now!
Bucky's become the same as that man.
Do it!
Hear it now!
Kill her!
You did it, Jinichi.
You were able to kill her.
How cruel of you.
Have you no heart left
inside of you, Maki?
I don't.
She took whatever heart I had with her.
Everyone says I'm a genius.
It's true, too.
I'm going to be the head of
the clan after my father.
I heard there's a loser in the Zenin clan.
They say the man ain't got a bit
of cursed energy in his whole body.
He must be really depressed.
I betcha that guy looks
pretty pathetic too.
Three, four, five, nine, ten, eleven.
You!
Ain't no Toji!
The sin of the insignificant
is the ignorance of strength.
No one was able to understand Toji.
Except maybe City Gojo.
But you ain't the one!
The one to stand among them!
Projection sources can't be used to create
movements that ignore
physics and trajectory.
There's a limit to how much acceleration
can be added to one's
speed upon activation.
The longer the technique
is continuously activated,
the further one can raise their speed.
No one to stand among them!
It's me!
I won't stop now.
I won't screw up like I did back then.
Force is wait-time speed.
She wants a Hidden fight, huh?
How about a hug?
I'll punch through her at top speed!
While Projection Sorcery is active,
anything the user touches
with their palm must
create a movement within
1 24th of a second.
If they fail, they'll be
frozen for one second.
She was probably planning to take
my attack and stop my movement,
even if it means I break her ribs.
It's like I'd fall for such obvious bait.
You really are an imposter!
24 times, right?
You and old man now,
Beat, aren't just fast.
There's something off about your speed.
You are creating 24 motions per second.
I can finally see it
after obtaining this body.
You imposter!
Sorry.
Can you repeat that?
Mother.
Mother stay away. Mother?
Why must you?
Always be like this?
If that's the way you feel.
Why?
Tell me to come back? huh?
What?
What are you talking about?
No. No. No. No.
Stupid bitch didn't end me.
Pathetic.
Are you kidding me?
I can't focus my cursed energy!
Damn gutter trash!
I'm glad I gave birth to you.
My!
This is why I told you not to go.
Please, take care of her.
What are you going to do now, Maki?
Thank you.
The darkness descends anew and
the lonely shadow lurks around.
Searching for its home in vain,
it's praying for redemption.
As pitiful and wretched as it is.
And slowly it begins,
seeds of hope bloom again.
You are growing colder,
your breath is growing rare.
I reach out my hand and
it cuts through the air.
Can we just go back to the way we were?
The ever-surging waves rushing in to
swallow me When I'm moving forward,
I destroy all that could be Will
the soothing end ever come for me?
So even if I get stabbed in the heart.
Or I get torn apart.
And then scattered around the world.
I don't care, cause I'm not afraid.
As I'm already empty inside.
Anyway, and so when the end has arrived?
Could you turn off the light?
I don't want anything anymore.
Cause if there's one thing that I do fear.
It's losing everything and everyone again.
Hakari was expelled for
clashing with the upper brass.
A fight club?
You don't talk about the fight club.
I can't get close Itadori you
snoop around from the inside.
I love it when you're hot!
Are you saying you want
to get high on my passion?